(Amy(on Skype):)Hi.
(Penny:)Hey, how'd it go?
Oh, great.
(Leonard:)Dr. Gallo is terrific.
(Sheldon:)You know,
I-I've always been insecure
(Leonard:)that no one cares
about what I have to say,
(Leonard:)but she made me see...
(Penny:)Yeah, no one cares.
Did you help me out or not?
Okay, n-now,
what I'm hearing
(Leonard:)is that you feel that
I sometimes take too long
(Leonard:)to express myself,
(Leonard:)and you wish
I'd be more succinct.
(Penny:)You're only hearing that because
(Penny:)I cannot roll my eyes
any louder.
(Leonard:)All right, well, after we talked
about my issues with my mother...
(Leonard:)nothing too deep,
just how she ruined my life...
(Leonard:)I told her about you
and your drug; she said
she'd be happy to meet you.
(Leonard:)Really?
(Penny:)Oh, you're the best
husband ever!
(Leonard:)So you'll go to the Doctor Who
convention with me next week?
(Sheldon:)I guess.
(Leonard:)Oh, I actually did hear
your eyes roll that time.
(vacuum whirring)
(Bernadette:)Boy, when was the last time
Stuart cleaned this place?
(Howard:)No kidding.
(Bernadette:)Oh, okay,
I'm about to suck something up.
(Howard:)What do you think
this object sounds like?